Yeah
EVERGLOW
Hit the drums Pa rum pum-pum-pum-pum-pum
Go ahead and sing Tra-la-la-la-la-la-la
I’m going in fierce from the start
Don’t be shocked
I’m spreading by word of mouth
They say that kid that just passed by isn’t average
This deep jungle is just a thrilling playground to me
Alright I’ve chosen
nananananana
I’ll leave my name in that heart of yours
So, You had better run
You are so done--
You are so done
Now you're done
Trapped in my light (Dun! Dun!)
Like a young lamb
Dun--
Baby you’ll be frozen
I’m more fearless than I look so strong
Don’t let down your guard or I’ll flip the tables
bomb, the bomb
I’ll dominate in a flash and leave you breathless
Talking cool but my gestures are hot like uh
Elegantly now I won't stop, can't stop I’m aiming for you
Even if you run it’s a deserted island
Alright it’s all over
nananananana
I’ll leave my image in that heart of yours
So, You had better run
You are so done--
Now you're done--
Trapped in my gaze (Dun! Dun!)
Like a young lamb
Dun--
Baby you’ll be frozen
Deeper and deeper I’ll dig into you
Clutching to the end without a doubt
Hail me (you’ll stare)
Shout my name (you’ll call)
That’s right (you’re mine)
I’ve seen right through you
You are so done--
Now you're done--
Trapped in my gaze (Dun! Dun!)
Like a young lamb
Dun--
Baby you’ll be frozen
(Dun! Dun!)